{"data":[{"question":"If anyone among them could sew, he\/she ___ a tablecloth for them all.","a":"would have made","b":"made","c":"had made","d":"will make","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past and the consequence if they had happened \n+ Form: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"It's time that you ___ home. I'd rather you ___ again tomorrow.","a":"go, are coming","b":"are going, will come","c":"would go, would come","d":"went, came","answer":"4","explain":"\n - It's time sbd did sth \n- Would rather sbd did sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Had then electric instruments not been invented, many problems of space flight ___.","a":"could not be solved","b":"could not have been solved","c":"could not have solved","d":"cannot be solved","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle \n- Sometimes conditional forms are inverted as a means of sounding more formal. In this case, the conditional 'if' is dropped and the inverted forms takes the place of the 'if clause' \n- Inversion clause: auxiliary + subject + main verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Why didn't anyone ring me up? \"Sorry, I lost your phone number; otherwise, I _________ long before.\"","a":"must have rung you up","b":"had rung you up","c":"ought have rung you up","d":"would have rung you up","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Would have PP: used when talking about something that did not happen, or a situation that cannot exist","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"I would have invited the new classmate to my birthday party but I ___ her well.","a":"didn't know","b":"don't know","c":"hadn't known","d":"doesn't know","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Would have PP: used when talking about something that did not happen, or a situation that cannot exist \n- Would have pp, simple past","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"It is important that an efficient worker ___ his\/her work on time.","a":"can finish","b":"finishes","c":"has finished","d":"finish","answer":"4","explain":"\n- It's important that somebody do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"___ you succeed in passing all the graduate school entrance examinations!","a":"Can","b":"May","c":"will","d":"Must","answer":"2","explain":"\n- May somebody\/something do something formal used to express a wish or hope","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"According to the examination, the victim ___ of murder.","a":"must have died","b":"would have died","c":"died","d":"would die","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Would have PP: used when talking about something that did not happen, or a situation that cannot exist ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The scholar ___ you if you ___ to visit him this afternoon.","a":"told, were going","b":"might tell, were going","c":"should have told, went","d":"might have told, had gone","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2 and 3: used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past which result in consequence at present \n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Our former history teacher died of cancer last term, otherwise she ___.","a":"should still work","b":"will still work","c":"would still be working","d":"would still have worked","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: used to talk about unlikely, imaginary or untrue events or situations \n- Form: if + Simple Past, would + Infinitive\/ be verb_ing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}